Finding Aid for Wilson Family Papers
William L. Clements Library, University of Michigan
- Wilson, William H.
  - Account Book, 1868 June 1-September 30 (Box 48)
Harrison, William (estate) 43:15
Harvey, John 43:22
Hattrick, Peter 43:16
Haven, Herman 43:23
Hicks, John D. 43:22
Hillsdale, [N.Y.] 43:23
Hoffman, Herman 43:22
Howard, Whitehead 43:21
Hull, Henry 43:22
Hyslop, John (estate) 43:23
Jackson, James ex dem Seth Jenkins 43:23
ex dem Frederick Myer 43:23
Jenta, Alexander 43:22
Kane, John R. 43:22
Kean, Paul 43:22
Kerr, Anthony 43:22, 23
King, E. C. 43:23
Lamb 43:23
Lamb, George C. 43:8, 26
Langhorn, William W. 43:22
Langlois, Charles 43:9, 17
Lewis, George 43:23
Lewis, Morgan 43:22
Livingston, Edward P. 43:22
Livingston, Emily M. 43:22
Livingston, Herman 43:22
Livingston, Maturin 43:22
Livingston, Robert R. 43:18, 22
Low, Isaac 43:23
Lynch, Dominick 43:19
Lynch, Henry 43:20, 21, 23
Lynk, Henry 43:29
Lynk, John 43:23
McLean, Augustus 43:22
March and Low (Co.) 43:22
Mason, George 43:23
Matthews, James 43:6
Miller, Adrian P. 43:23
Minor, Eunice 43:22
Monell, George 43:22
Moore, Thomas 43:22
More, Jacob J. 43:22
Munn, Stephen B. 43:23
Murray, Robert I. 43:23
New York City 43:23
Norton, John L. 43:22, 23, 27, 28
Norton, Samuel I. L. 43:23
Olcott, John L. 43:22
Page, William S. 43:19
Palmer, Levi 43:22
Parker, John 43:23
Parker, Miles 43:22
Peltier and Morel 43:22
Racy, Charles 43:23
Read, Samuel 43:23
Reade, Morris 43:23, 25
Reformed Protestant Dutch Church of the City of New York 43:16
Rifenburgh, George M. 43:23
Roe, Walter 43:22
Rogers, Benjamin W. 43:23
Rogers, Edward N. et al. 43:22, 23
Rogers, Samuel 43:22
Ross, John 43:24
Schermerhorn, Jacob 43:22
Schoonmaker, David 43:23
Scott, Moses 43:23
Scriba, [George?] 43:22
Scriba and Schroeppel 43:23
Scrugham, William W. 43:23
Shelden, Dudley 43:7
Semon and Becker 43:23
Siem and Van Beuren 43:22
Sims, William L. 43:22
Skidmore, Joel 43:22
Slocomb, Jared 43:24
Slosson, William 43:22
Smith, John P. 43:25
Snyder 43:23
Songlass, Isaac 43:23
Spoor, David 43:22
Steitz, Lewis 43:22
Stevens 43:23
Stiles, John 43:22
Stone, Frederick W. 43:26
Teiter, Zacharia 43:23
Ten Broeck, Jacob 43:22
Thompson, William A. 43:23
Thomson, A. 43:27
Tice, John 43:28
Tompkins, William 43:22
Valkenburgh, Christian 43:22
Van Alstyne, William 43:22
Van Beuren and Lawrence 43:22
Van Ness, Jacob 43:23, 29, 30
Van Ness, Peter 43:23
Van Vechter, John (heirs of) 43:23
Van Wickle, Evert 43:23
Villagrand, Jerome J. d' 43:23
Vriers, Jacob 43:22
Wagner, Peter et al 43:22
Waldo, Samuel 43:22
Wallach 43:23
Walter, Henry 43:18, 30
Warner, Henry 43:23
Webb, John I. 43:11
Willard, John M. 43:12
Williams, Jonas 43:22
Wilson, George 43:23
Wilson, Peter 43:22
Wilson, William H. 43:22
Wiltsie, Conrad 43:23
Wiswall, Enoch 43:22, 23
Woodward, John 43:22
Wycoff, Ferdinand 43:22
Estates (Law)--New York (State)
Broadhead, J. O. 41:29
Broadhead, Thomas 41:29
Cockburn, James 7:5, 19; 10:79; 41:31
Crawford, George 41:29
Cupper, Henry 41:29
Dibblee, Eliza, Wilson 41:29
Flowers, Samuel 41:29
Greenleaf, Thomas 41:29
Hoffman, Philip 41:29
Hister, Sarah Hulme 41:29
Howey, Francis 41:29
Hubbard, Edward 41:29
Livingston, Betsey n.d. 42:7
Livingston, Edward P., 1779-1843 42:7
Livingston, Peter R., 1742-1794 42:7
Livingston, Philip n.d. 42:7
Livingston, Robert, 1654-1728 42:7
Livingston, Robert Jr., 1708-1790 42:7
Livingston, Robert Cambridge, 1742-1794 5:56, 71; 6:24, 67; 8:50, 70; 11:72; 15:47; 25:51;42:1, 2
Livingston, Robert R., 1746-1813 22:57; 29:24; 42:3, 4, 5, 6
Livingston, Peter R., 1737-1794 42:7
Livingston, Walter T., 1772-1827 42:7
Livingston, William S. n.d. 42:7
Norton 42:8
Owens, Zeba L. 42:8
Ray, Cornelius 42:8
Rutsen, Cott Jacob 42:8
Salles, Laurent 42:8
Sanders, Jane E. Livingston 42:8
Sloan, Rachel 42:8
Ten Broeck, Dirk Wessells 42:8
Ten Broeck, Samuel 42:8
Turner, John 42:8
Van Rensselaer, Maunsell 42:8
Weaver, William 42:8
Wilson, Alexander, 1783-1805 15:4; 42:8
Wilson, Mary Thong Livingston, 1783-1841 42:8
Wilson, Robert L., 1794-1830 42:9
Wilson, William, 1756-1828 28:91; 33:8, 10, 15, 17; 34:34; 42:10
Wimple, Walter V. 42:8